gatewaytomilwaukee.com 2008-09-14

# The Gateway To Milwaukee

We believe that your privacy and confidentiality is very important. Consequently, we have set a very high standard in safeguarding your personal information and will protect the information you share with us. Our privacy applies to all information that we collect at this website, in telephone conversations, e-mail transactions, and through in-person order placement. The content of your documents will remain private.

**Your Responsibility**  
When using this website, you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this security and privacy policy. To do a better job protecting your privacy needs, and to adapt to new laws, legal standards, and printing industry standards and customs, we will periodically review our Security and Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to make changes, modifications, alterations, and updates to this policy at any time. If changes are made, we will not contact you. It is your responsibility to personally check the Security and Privacy Policy for changes, modifications, alterations, and updates.

**Customer Information**  
When you become our customer, you may be asked to provide us with certain information, including your company name, your name, and your e-mail address. This information will be used for unspecified updates and communications about your order, questionnaires to measure your satisfaction, and announcements of new products, services, and special pricing promotions.

**Security and Privacy**  
We will not share any of your company or personal information or data with any of our partners or vendors. It is our policy to protect your information from all types of loss, misuse, or alteration. Any artwork files or documents submitted will be treated with respect and the utmost care. However, we remind all customers that no electronic transaction is ever 100% guaranteed-service.

**Cookie Files**  
In order to provide you with the best website experience possible, we may store non-critical information about you by embedding cookies on your computer hard drive. Some of our strategic partners, such as those with links to our website, may use cookies, but we are not responsible for the abuse or misuse of any information gathered through the use of cookies by such third parties.

**Free Newsletters, Announcements, Contests, and Surveys**  
We may contact you from time to time to provide you with a free newsletter or to make you aware of special offers, pricing promotions, surveys, or contests. Your participation is strictly voluntary. You may request that your name be removed from our list at any time. Any information we may gather by these means will be used to provide better service and customer-care. We will not share any of this information with others.

If you have any questions, comments, or feedback about our Security and Privacy Policy, please [contact us.](mailto:mbyrne@gatewaytomilwaukee.com?subject=From%20Privacy%20%2F%20Security%20Page%20on%20Gateway%20To%20Milwaukee%20website)
